latestays.com 2012-09-20

# Asia Web Direct.com: Privacy

## Our Privacy Policy

At LateStays.com, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of any personally identifiable information ("PII") you provide us. PII includes information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, phone number, or email address.

This Privacy Policy explains how we handle and protect your PII in accordance with internationally recognised privacy principles. This policy was last adjusted on 12 February 2009. 

We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time and for any reason. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this website. Questions regarding this policy should be emailed to [privacy@asiawebdirect.com](mailto:privacy@asiawebdirect.com?subject=\[privacy%20policy\])

What information we collect
    In an effort to keep our service as simple and easy to use as possible we do not create, use or store profiles of our customers. We only record PII and other information that we reasonably require to do business with you. more info
How we use your information
    We use your PII only for the purpose of responding to and fulfilling your requests for our products and services. more info
Who we share your information with
    We do not disclose any information about customer bookings to anyone for purposes which are not related to your booking or the delivery of our services to you. more info
How you control and access your information
    We believe that site visitors and customers should have control over the collection and use of their PII more info
How we protect your information
    To ensure the confidentiality of your PII, we use leading security technology and procedures that are regularly reviewed and updated. more info

## What Information We Collect

In an effort to keep our service as simple and easy to use as possible, we do not create, use or store profiles of our customers. We only record PII and other information that we reasonably require to do business with you. On all our web pages that collect PII, we specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service you request. 

We collect PII when you:

  * _Make a booking_  
We collect your full name, email address and phone number each time you make a booking on our site. We will also collect credit card information, including card number, card type, security number, cardholder name, billing address and expiry date to pay for accommodation purchased through our site.
  * _Subscribe to our newsletter_  
We use your email address when you make a booking on our site or request a downloadable travel guide to subscribe you to our AsiaWebDirect newsletter. You are free to unsubscribe to our newsletter at any time (see below for how to unsubscribe).
  * _Surveys, promotions and competition information_  
Occasionally, We may offer site visitors or newsletter recipients an opportunity to participate in a survey, promotion or competition. The PII we collect when you participate in a survey, promotion or competition may include your full name, email address, telephone number and street address.
  * _Contact with us_  
We collect PII such as your full name, email address and/or telephone number whenever you submit an enquiry or suggestion, or request assistance with a booking. 

Other information we collect:

  * _Statistical information_  
When you visit our site, we record general information about your visit for statistical purposes. These statistics do not contain any PII. 
  * _IP address_  
When you visit our site our web server automatically records the IP address of your computer (location on the Internet) to assist with fraud protection. 
  * _Cookies_  
We may, from time to time, use "cookies" to store your preferences, record session information and collect information on how you visit and access our web pages. We collect information on the web pages visited by our customers to help us continue to improve our services. 

Cookies are pieces of information that our web page transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them to provide useful features for you. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify you, only your computer.

You can delete cookies from your computer at any time (see your internet browser's help menu for more information); however, this will remove all cookies and not just those associated with our site. You can individually remove a cookie that connects a property to your shortlist by clicking the remove option when the property appears in your shortlist.

## How We Use Your Information

We use your PII only for the purpose of responding to and fulfilling your requests for our products and services. Information collected on our site may be used to:

  * _Purchase of products or services_  
Information collected when you purchase from us is used to charge your credit card and deliver your booking confirmation electronically. We may also contact you about your stay for customer service purposes or to make any changes or cancellations to your booking.
  * _Send newsletter email_  
We will only send newsletters to people that have opted in to receive them. Our newsletters provide information about the latest deals available on our website, and occassionally offer incentives for completing surveys or participating in competitions or promotions.
  * _Communications with you_  
We will use your email address and/or telephone number to contact you when you submit a question or suggestion or if we have a need to contact you in connection with your booking.We may use your email address and booking information to inform you of additional services and special offers, and to build features that will make the service easier and more personalized for you to use. At your request, we will not send any information or offers unrelated to your specific booking. At your request, we will send your booking information to your email address or other nominated contact method subject to our customer identity verification procedures being satisfied.
  * _Fraud protection_  
We may pass on your credit card information and IP address to our fraud screening services provider to assist with protecting against fraud.

## Who We Share Your Information With

We do not disclose any information about customer bookings to anyone except in the following circumstances:

  * _Accommodation suppliers_  
We provide the guest name, telephone number and email address for each booking made to the relevant accommodation supplier. Our accommodation suppliers require this information for the booking and may use it if they need to contact you about the booking. We may also pass on your credit card information via a secure password protected page to the accommodation supplier solely for purposes of guaranteeing your booking or for the supplier to charge part of the booking amount (if applicable). 
  * _Payment processing_  
We pass on through the secure payment gateway your credit card information and billing address to the bank which processes your payment. We may pass on your credit card information and IP address (location on the Internet) to our fraud screening service provider. 
  * _Company group members_  
We may pass on your personal information to our other group companies (being related bodies corporate of Asia Web Direct (HK) Limited) for the purposes of assisting with your booking and performing related activities as described in this Privacy Policy. 
  * _Legal obligations_  
We may be required by law to disclose information you provide to us. We may also disclose information against someone who poses a threat to our interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could cause harm to others.

## How You Control and Access Your Information

We believe that site visitors and customers should have control over the collection and use of their PII. Here's how you can control and have access to your information:

  * _Newsletter subscription and unsubscription_  
If at any time you would like to either change your email address with us or unsubscribe from our newsletter you can: 
    1. Go to the "Newsletter" section of our site from the home page and follow the instructions to change your email address or unsubscribe; or 
    2. Send an email to [newsletter@asiawebdirect.com](mailto:newsletter@asiawebdirect.com?subject=\[newsletter%20subscription%20changes\]) advising that you would like to unsubscribe or change your email address. Be sure to include details of your old and new email addresses for changes.
  * _Booking information_  
If at any time you would like to alter the PII you provided us in your booking, please [contact us](http://www.asiawebdirect.com/customer/enquiry/?page=LateStays.com).
  * _Remember my details for next time_  
If at any time you would like us to stop remembering your details for the next time you book, untick "Remember my details for next time" the next time you make a booking, or [contact us](http://www.asiawebdirect.com/customer/enquiry/?page=LateStays.com).
  * _General_  
If at any time you want to enquire about any of your PII that we store, please [contact us](http://www.asiawebdirect.com/customer/enquiry/?page=LateStays.com).

## How We Protect Your Information

To ensure the confidentiality of your PII, we use leading security technology and procedures that are regularly reviewed and updated. 

We have also obtained a digital certificate from the VeriSign group, an industry leader in the protection and management of data transmission.

Our systems are configured with industry standard data encryption and firewall technology. When you send PII to us over the Internet, your data is protected by Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure safe transmission.
